Class of 1898 Records, 1894-1969
Smith College Archives
Class of 1898 Records
1894-1969
Smith College. Class of 1898.
RG 80 UUID:1808bb33-9b55-463d-8e69-a13aa10f8003
19 boxes (10.2 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection is in 19 boxes and contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1898.
The Class of 1898 was the twentieth entering class and the twentieth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1898 records, 1894-1969, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1898, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, correspondences, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1898 records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Baccalaureate Service 1898 (Box 1552, Folder 1)
- Bookplate 1939 (Box 1552, Folder 2)
- Commencement 1898 (Box 1552, Folder 3)
- Commencement Music 1898 (Box 1552, Folder 4)
- Commencement Photographs 1898 (Box 1552, Folder 5)
- Essay Prize Committee undated (Box 1552, Folder 6)
- Freshman Grind by 1897 1894 (Box 1552, Folder 7)
- Groups 1894-1898 (Box 1552, Folder 8)
- History 1898-1905 (Box 1552, Folder 9)
- Ivy Day 1898 (Box 1552, Folder 10)
- Ivy Day Photographs 1898 (Box 1552, Folder 11)
- Junior Prom 1897 (Box 1552, Folder 12)
- Junior Reception 1897 (Box 1552, Folder 13)
- Junior Ushers 1897 (Box 1552, Folder 14)
- Class Letters 1924-1958 (Box 1552, Folder 15)
- Reunion 1899 (Box 1553, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1900 (Box 1553, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1903 (Box 1553, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1908 (Box 1553, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1913 (Box 1553, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1918 (Box 1553, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1923 (Box 1553, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1928 (Box 1553, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1933 (Box 1553, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1938 (Box 1553, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1943 (Box 1553, Folder 11)
- Reunions 1948 (Box 1553, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1950 (Box 1553, Folder 13)
- Reunions 1953 (Box 1553, Folder 14)
- Reunions 1963 (Box 1553, Folder 15)
- Reunion Correspondence 1963 (Box 1553, Folder 16)
- Reunions 1968 (Box 1553, Folder 17)
- Reunions 1969 (Box 1553, Folder 18)
- Reunion Songs undated (Box 1553, Folder 19)
- Sophomore Reception 1894 (Box 1553, Folder 20)
- Sophomore-Senior Entertainment 1896 (Box 1553, Folder 21)
- Class Supper 1898 (Box 1553, Folder 22)
- Songs 1894-1898 (Box 1553, Folder 23)
- Student Rooms undated (Box 1553, Folder 24)
- Scrapbook 1894-1898 (Box 1554)
- Scrapbook 1894-1898 (Box 1554)
- Reunion Guest book 1898-1963 (Box 1554)
- Senior Dramatics 1898 (Box 1555, Folder 1)
- Senior Dramatics: Photographs 1898 (Box 1555, Folder 2)
- Senior Dramatics: Photographs 1898 (Box 1555, Folder 3)
- Senior Dramatics: Photographs 1898 (Box 1555, Folder 4)
- Memorabilia (Box OV)